localstore.co.uk 2012-12-29

# Privacy - LocalStore

Privacy Policy

LocalStore.co.uk is owned and operated by Prime Space Marketing Pty Limited. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

We gather two types of information about users: Information that you provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because we derive our revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users.

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by you:

1\. Electronic newsletters  
We offer a free electronic newsletter to you. We gather your email address of users if you voluntarily subscribe. You may remove yourself from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points you to the subscription management page.

2\. User Reviews  
Users of the Review System must register separately for the services in order to post reviews. During registration the user may be required to supply one or more of the following: a username, password, and/or an email address.

3\. E-mail to a friend Service  
You can choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". You must provide your email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

4\. Polling  
We may offer interactive polls to you so you can easily share your opinions with others and see what our audience thinks about important issues. We may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question.

5\. Surveys  
We may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners.

We track user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).

We sometimes track and catalogue the search terms that users enter in our Search function. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser however this means you may not be able to access the site.

We use any information voluntarily given by you to enhance your experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalised elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on your interests.

We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs.

From time to time we may disclose your information to our advertisers, service providers and contractors to help us to provide and market our/their goods and services to you. We may also share your information with third parties who provide prizes for competitions or special offers. If we do this we generally require these parties to protect your information in the same way we do.

We operate secure data networks protected by industry standard firewall and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary and only authorised individuals have access to the information provided by you.

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include: Opting not to register to receive our electronic newsletters. Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users

Please contact us to ask for access to any of your information or if you have a complaint concerning your privacy.
